
{"questionlist":[
{"cardfront":"concat( )",
"cardback":"Joins two or more arrays, and returns a copy of the joined arrays"
},
{"cardfront":"copyWithin( )",
"cardback":"Copies array elements within the array, to and from specified positions"
},
{"cardfront":"entries( )",
"cardback":"Returns a key/value pair Array Iterations Object"
},
{"cardfront":"every( )",
"cardback":"Checks if every element in an array pass a test"
},
{"cardfront":"fill()",
"cardback":"Fill the elements in an array with a static value"
},
{"cardfront":"filter( )",
"cardback":"Creates a new array with every element in an array that pass a test"
},
{"cardfront":"find( )",
"cardback":"Returns the value of the first element in an array that pass a test"
},
{"cardfront":"findIndex( )",
"cardback":"Returns the index of the first element in an array that pass a test"
},
{"cardfront":"forEach( )",
"cardback":"Calls a funciton for each array element"
},
{"cardfront":"from( )",
"cardback":"Creates an array from an object"
},
{"cardfront":"includes( )",
"cardback":"Check if an array contains the specified element"
},
{"cardfront":"indexOf( )",
"cardback":"Search the array fro an element and reurns its position"
},
{"cardfront":"isArray( )",
"cardback":"Checks whether an object is an array"
},
{"cardfront":"join( )",
"cardback":"Joins all elements of an array into a string"
},
{"cardfront":"keys( )",
"cardback":"Returns a Array Iteration Object, containing the keys of the original array"
},
{"cardfront":"lastIndexOf( )",
"cardback":"Search the array for an element, starting at the end, and returns its position"
},
{"cardfront":"map( )",
"cardback":"Creates a new array with the result of calling a funcion for each array element"
},
{"cardfront":"pop( )",
"cardback":"Removes the last element of an array, and returns that element"
},
{"cardfront":"push( )",
"cardback":"Adds new elements to the end of an array, and returns the new length"
},
{"cardfront":"reduce( )",
"cardback":"Reduce the values of an array to a single value (going left-to-right)"
},
{"cardfront":"reduceRight( )",
"cardback":"Reduce the values of an array to a single value (going right-to-left)"
},
{"cardfront":"reverse( )",
"cardback":"Reverses the order of the elements in an array"
},
{"cardfront":"slice( )",
"cardback":"Selects a part of an array, and returns the new array"
},
{"cardfront":"some( )",
"cardback":"Checks if any of the elements in an array pass a test"
},
{"cardfront":"sort( )",
"cardback":"Sorts the elements of an array"
},
{"cardfront":"splice( )",
"cardback":"Adds/Removes elements from an array"
},
{"cardfront":"toString( )",
"cardback":"Converts an array to a string, and returns the result"
},
{"cardfront":"unshift( )",
"cardback":"Adds new elements to the beginning of an array, and returns the new length"
},
{"cardfront":"valueOf( )",
"cardback":"Returns the primitive value of an array"
}
]}
